<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<doc><id>2019013752959</id><url>https://www.3dmgame.com/news/201901/3752959.html</url><title>跃跃欲试了吗？《生化危机2重制版》全奖杯列表曝光</title><datetime>2019-01-06 09:57:4</datetime><text>
	距离万众瞩目的《生化危机重制版》正式发售只有不到1个月的时间，已经有不少零售商偷跑的消息，而在知名论坛PSNProfile上，游戏的完整奖杯列表也被曝光，让我们一起来看一下即将迎接的挑战吧。








	Raccoon City Native – Obtain all trophies – Platinum


完成所有奖杯——白金


	A Hero Emerges – Complete Leon’s story – Silver


完成里昂故事——银


	A Heroine Emerges – Complete Claire’s story – Silver


完成克莱尔故事——银


	Hip to Add Squares – Increase your inventory slots – Bronze


增加你的物品栏上限——铜


	Don’t Need No Stinkin’ Gun – Defeat an enemy with a knife – Bronze


用匕首杀死一名敌人——铜


	That’ll Hold ‘Em – Use Wooden Boards to board up a window – Bronze


用木板钉一次窗户——铜


	A Vault-like Mind – Open a portable safe – Bronze


打开次元箱——铜


	First Break-In – Open a dial safe – Bronze


打开一个保险箱——铜


	Bon Appetit – Shoot the grenade you fed to an enemy – Bronze


往敌人嘴里塞手雷堵住然后射击引爆——铜


	Zombie Roundup – Kill 3 enemies at once with a sub-weapon – Bronze


用副武器一次性杀死3名敌人——铜


	Like Skeet Shooting – Shoot a zombie dog or a licker out of the air – Bronze


射击跳跃在空中的敌人——铜


	Keep Their Heads Ringin’ – Paralyse a licker’s sense of hearing – Bronze


使舔食者的听觉瘫痪——铜


	Hats Off! – Shoot Tyrant’s hat off his head – Bronze


把暴君头上的帽子打下来——铜


	Treasure Hunter – Using the photo hints, find 2 hidden items – Bronze


使用照片提示找到两个隐藏物品——铜


	A Waist of Space – Expand inventory slots to max – Bronze


把物品栏扩充到最大——铜


	Lore Explorer – Read all of the files – Bronze


阅读所有文件——铜


	Complete Vermin Extermination – Destroy all Mr. Raccoons – Silver


毁掉所有浣熊玩偶——银


	Master of Unlocking – Open all safes and locks in the game – Silver


打开所有的密码锁和保险箱——银


	Hardcore Rookie – Complete Leon’s story on “Hardcore” game mode – Gold


完成里昂硬核模式——金


	Hardcore College Student – Complete Claire’s story on “Hardcore” game mode – Gold


完成克莱尔硬核模式——金


	Frugalist – Complete the game without using a recovery item – Silver


不使用恢复道具通关游戏——银


	Minimalist – Clear the game without opening the item box – Silver


不开箱完成游戏——银


	A Small Carbon Footprint – Take 14000 steps or fewer in one playthrough – Silver


完成游戏时计步器少于14000——银


	Never-Ending Rain – Escape the police station – Bronze


逃离警察站——铜


	Hack Complete – Complete Ada’s Segment – Bronze


完成艾达部分——铜


	The Basics of Survival – Combine two items together – Bronze


把两个道具组合在一起——铜


	Customizer – Customize a weapon – Bronze


强化武器——铜


	Eat This! – Counterattack with a sub-weapon – Bronze


用副武器反击——铜


	Vermin Extermination – Destroy a Mr. Raccoon – Bronze


摧毁一个浣熊玩偶——铜


接下来是隐藏奖杯列表：


Welcome to the city of the Dead – Make it to the police station. – Bronze


去警局——铜


	Path to the Goddess – Solve the Goddess Statue puzzle. – Bronze


解开女神雕像的谜题——铜


	Hide and Seek – Complete Sherry’s segment. – Bronze


完成雪莉部分——铜


	A Great Need for a Shower – Escape from the sewers. – Bronze


从下水道逃离——铜


	Broken Umbrella – Witness the true ending. – Bronze


见证真结局——铜


	Gotcha! – Defeat Stage 2 G using the crane only once. – Bronze


用一个起重机击败G2——铜


	One Slick Super-spy – Use only the EMF Visualizer to complete Ada’s gameplay segment. – Bronze


只使用EMF完成艾达部分——铜


	Young Escape – Escape the bedroom within 60 seconds during Sherry’s segment. – Bronze


在60s内逃离卧室——铜


	With Time to Spare – Defeat Stage 4 G with 4+ minutes left until detonation. – Bronze


在打败G4前还剩余4分钟以上的时间——铜


	In The Blink of an Eye – Defeat Super Tyrant with 5+ minutes left until detonation. – Bronze


击败完全体暴君时还剩余5分钟以上时间——铜


	Leon “S.” Kennedy – Complete Leon’s story on “Standard” or “Hardcore” with an S rank. – Bronze


标准或硬核模式通关里昂故事时达到S评价——铜


	Sizzling Scarlet hero – Complete Claire’s story on “Standard” or “Hardcore” with an S rank. – Bronze


标准或硬核模式通关克莱尔故事时达到S评价——铜


	Grim Reaper – Complete “The 4th Survivor” extra mode. – Bronze


完成第四幸存者模式——铜


 


以上就是《生化危机重制版》的完整奖杯列表，游戏将于1月25日上线，小伙伴们是否已经摩拳擦掌起来了？

</text><imageurl>https://img.3dmgame.com/uploads/images/news/20190106/1546739757_532492.png	https://img.3dmgame.com/uploads/images/news/20190106/1546739761_686826.png	https://img.3dmgame.com/uploads/images/news/20190106/1546739818_403659.jpeg	</imageurl><videourl /></doc>